Whenever I go out of India to another country,
my maximum
duration should be 30 days and
I should return to India within 30 days.
Once you come back to India then again you can
fly from India to abroad and again you
can stay for 30 days.  This will be
continuing for a period of one year.
You can go on any number of trips in a year.
But the maximum trip duration should not
exceed the limit that has been taken by the
customer during the purchase of the policy.
And as I inform you there are 76 covers, base place
extensions, so there is the normal classification
where there are medical covers, accidental and
disability covers, baggage and personal
effects covers, other covers, missed
journey covers and travel delay and cancellation
covers. These are the categorization of the types of
covers that have been there.  So
in hospitalization covers you have six base covers and
six extension covers.  Some of the
example covers are OPD, Physiotherapy and
Medical Aid.  These are the six extension covers
and hospitalization cover either repatriation
or medical evacuation these will be coming
under the base covers.  There are total 12 covers
in Medical Expenses & Accidental &
Disabilities. We have four base covers
and four extension covers.  Common carrier
cover is Coma cover and Child benefit cover which are
the extension covers and base
covers like personal accident
or death and disability due to common
carrier.  This will be coming under the
base covers.  And third is my baggage and
personal effects.  There are seven base
covers in this and five extensions.  The loss
of checked-in baggage, delay of checked-in baggage or
damage to baggage, out of these three, the first
two will come under the base covers.  And
sports equipment cover, loss of
valuables including personal money and damage
to baggage during transit which will be coming
under the extension part of the
product.  And travel delay and trip
cancellation like our trip cancellation is covered
or trip interaction due to cut off.
These are the two These are the base covers
and so on we have approximately 14 base
covers and five extension covers.  Some
of the extension covers are trip resumption,
refund of frequent flyer points,
hotel bookings on bounced flights.
These are my trip delay covers that will
come.  Missed Shore Covers This will come under Cruise.
If you opt for cruise cover and
cruise interruption or cruise cover news and
excursion cover this will be covered these are the
few covers under cruise and other
covers as I told you you have pet
care cover or your
travel loan secured wala international
driving license cover or your
upgradation of business class wala cover these are few other
covers which are been added and
here you will get an
extension cover 19 base covers and coming
to the stand out features product.  The first
thing we cover is pre-disease
during life threatening conditions.  And
secondly, we also cover pet care and veterinary
hospitalization.  Where
your stomach is either travelling towards you
or not.  In both the
aspects we have the pet care covered.  And
sublimate whenever the customer is opting
for sublimate and he has the option to not
opt ​​out of the sublimate where his
supplements will not be applicable but a
bit of premium will be higher.
Next, these are some of our more specific
standard features, as I mentioned,
we cover adventure sports
in retail, which very few companies
cover as of today.  and Car Rental Covers Cruise
Covers and Trip Cancellation Due to Visa
Rejection and Refund of Visa Fee
Covers.  These are the covers which we provide
in for the moderate travels which are
not shared source by most of the
insurance companies and
Vikrant we have your voice sabka awaaz nahi aa raha no no nothing much
one second
ok
cover I have said diseases which is ours that will be
covered under following conditions only and
pre-existing disease cover is an
extension part of the cover which includes hospitalization expenses and there are some
limits that are given for pre-existing
disease cover based on the age band of the
customer.  So preying diseases will be covered.
And this should be declared before the policy
purchase from the customer.
Ok?
And as I mentioned, pet care
cover, we have a feature where if you
see another pet is traveling with you or not with
you, that will be covered.  That is
coverage for medical expenses.  If your pet
is hospitalized or injured while under the
care of a designated AH Care giveaway
during a trip upriver.  That is if your
pet is left with someone else and
there is some injury or you are
hospitalized
for the injury then the
coverage will be provided even when
you are abroad.  Even if you are taking it
with you for the journey abroad.  If there are any
medical expenses due to the pet
injury then that will be covered.  And the next
next thing is ah sublime waver part.
Like supplements there are some
supplements that are applicable under the
policy Hospitalization Hospital room
₹1800 up to 30 days and Intensive care
unit ₹3250 per day for six days Surgical
treatment ₹1000 Anesthesia treatment
25% off the surgical treatment and
Physician visit
₹100
So these are some supplements that are
applicable under the policy if the customer is
opting for the supplement then it is
ok and he or she also has the chance
to opt out of the sublimit where
they do not have any sublimits.
And adventure sports cover which we
provide as I already explained to
you there are around 100 plus adventure
sports that are covered under the Trip
Plus policy.  Near are the few of the
examples that are being displayed here.
One is walking over 2000 meters altitude,
big game hunting, bus touring, yachting,
martial arts, weightlifting, sailing,
zip lining, marathon, desert running, dusk climbing, ice skating,
power lifting. These are few examples that are being covered here and during
the adventure sports
hospitalization expenses and so ah
personal accident experiences are covered hospitalization expenses if
you are
participating in adventure sports and you have got any
injury and something there
you get hospitalization hospitalization
if something happens then at that time the adventure
sports cover gets into the picture and so with
the personal accident you have to be
the personal accident where the disability and so any other
mishap is happened here personal
accident due to adventure sports cover
will get into the action and car rental cover
if the car is reimbursed as a car rental car
insurance if the vehicle is stolen and
Damage in the Cogen and Cover Threat Damage excluding
any other deductible and Car
Rental Cover for Deductible Reimbursements Deductible
Amount Here Car Rental
Cover will give the reimbursement if
the car has been damaged and stolen and you are
able to return it to the respectable
owner of the custom car who is the one who has rented
you the vehicle excluding the deductible.
You have to pay the deductible in the first cover.
In the second cover, the deductible is also
paid by the IL company.  This is the basic
difference between the cartel cover for deduction
and car rental cover.  And medical cover and
cruise as I told you there is hospitalization cover
also.  Cruise Whenever you go overseas, you are
travelling by cruise
from point B to point C, then if
you get hospitalized then there will be
coverage for
hospitalization expenses during the
cruise along with the daily allowance if
paid out where you will also get money in daily allowance
for every 24 hours when whenever you are
injured and medical evacuation
if your treatment is not about to happen
on the cruise due to the
medical availability on the cruise and
you have to shift to the nearest hospital
for the better treatment that will be coming
under the medical evacuation.  So that the
transportation charges from the hospital to
the nearest hospital will be covered
under the medical part. Unused
Excursion Refund of the missed pre-booking
excursion due to the hospitalization.  If
you are hospitalized and that is the
reason you are some what do you say?
Shires and so excursions on the cruise than that will be
rebus by the company
and missed shore cover if